question_data = [

            {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

            {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
             "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False",
             "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Rapper Snoop Dogg&#039;s real name is &#039;Cordozar Calvin "
                         "Broadus, Jr.&#039;.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "In World War II, Hawker Typhoons served in the Pacific theater.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
             "question": "The IBM PC used an Intel 8008 microprocessor clocked at 4.77 MHz and 8 kilobytes of memory.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "One of Donald Trump&#039;s 2016 Presidential Campaign promises was to build a border wall between the United States and Mexico.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
             "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ", "correct_answer": "False",
             "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean",
             "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "Waylon Smithers from &quot;The Simpsons&quot; was originally black when he first appeared in the series.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
             "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
             "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
            {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
             "difficulty": "medium",
             "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade "
                         "launcher.",
             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
